en:
  shared:
    uti_ssi_questionnaire:
      subsections:
        "2": "2. Urological risk factors (present at the time UTI/SSI was diagnosed)"

        "3":
          text: "3. Urological intervention"
          question: "Urological intervention which according to the investigator lead to the current episode of UTI/SSI"
        "4": "4. Clinical information about the UTI/SSI"
        "5":
          uti: "5. Microbiological information about the current episode of UTI"
          ssi: "5. Microbiological information about the current episode of SSI"
        "6":
          uti: "6. Antimicrobial treatment for the current episode of UTI"
          ssi: "6. Antimicrobial treatment for the current episode of SSI"

      previous:
        question:
          uti: "Previous UTI (within last 12 months)"
          ssi: "Previous SSI (within last 12 months)"
      tractobstruction:
        question: "Urinary tract obstruction (any level) or reflux considered to be a significant risk factor for the current infection"
      tractobjstructionspeficy:
        question: "Please specify"
        help: "English text"
      urinarystones:
        question: "Urinary stones (more than one location can be reported)"
        answers:
          calyceal: "Calcyceal"
          renalpelvic: "Renal pelvic"
          ureteral: "Ureteral"
          bladder: "Bladder"
      treatment:
        question: "Antibiotic treatment for any reason within the previous 3 months"
      treatmentspeficy:
        question: "Please specify diagnosis"
        help: "English text"
      hospitalisation:
        question: "Hospitalisation for any reason within the last 6 months"
      catheter:
        question:
          uti: "Catheter at the time when UTI was diagnosed (more than one location can be reported)"
          ssi: "Catheter at the time when SSI was diagnosed (more than one location can be reported)"
        answers:
          urethral: "Urethral"
          suprapubic: "Suprapubic"
          ureteralstent: "Ureteral stent"
          nephrostomy: "Nephrostomy"
          others: "Others"
      catheterduration:
        question:
          uti: "Duration of catheter usage (in days) at the time UTI was diagnosed"
          ssi: "Duration of catheter usage (in days) at the time SSI was diagnosed"
        append: "days"
        help: "(e.g. 20). Enter 0 if no catheter was used."

      intervention_endoscopic:
        quesion: "Endoscopic"
        answers:
          Cystoscopy: "Cystoscopy"
          Diagnostic_ureterorenoscopy: "Diagnostic Ureterorenoscopy"
          TUR-P: "TUR-P"
          TUR-BT: "TUR-BT"
          URS_with_stone_treatment: "URS with stone treatment"
          PCNL: "PCNL"
          ureteral_stent_placement: "Ureteral stent placement"
      intervention_percutaneous:
        question: "Percutaneous"
        answers: "Percutaneous nephrostomy placement"
      intervention_laparoscopic:
        question: "Laparoscopic and robot assisted procedures"
        answers:
          kidney_abdominal_testis: "On kidney and abdominal testis"
          Lymph_node_dissection: "Lymph node dissection"
          Prostatectomy: "Prostatectomy"
          Cystectomy_and_urinary_diversion: "Cystectomy and urinary diversion/bladder replacement with bowel segments"
          Other: "Other"
      intervention_opensurgery:
        question: "Open surgery"
        answers:
          Vasectomy: "Vasectomy"
          Inguinal_scrotal_and_penile: "Inguinal, scrotal and penile"
          RPLND: "RPLND"
          Open_prostatectomy: "Open prostatectomy (for BPH)"
          Simple_nephrectomy: "Simple nephrectomy"
          Radical_nephrectomy: "Radical nephrectomy"
          RRP: "RRP"
          Cystectomy_and_urinary_diversion: "Cystectomy and urinary diversion/bladder replacement with bowel segments"
      prostatebiopsy:
        question: "Prostate biopsy"
        answers:
          transrectal: "Transrectal"
          perineal: "Perineal"
      trus_biopsy:
        quesion: "TRUS biopsy"
        help: "English text"
      intervention_others:
        quesion: "Others"
        answers: "ESWL"
      intervention_contamination:
        question:
          uti: "Contamination status of the intervention which according to the investigator lead to the current episode of UTI"
          ssi: "Contamination status of the intervention which according to the investigator lead to the current episode of SSI"
        answers:
          clean: "Clean (no infection present in the operative field or urinary tract, and bowel not opened)"
          cleancontaminated: "Clean-contaminated (no infection present but urinary tract opened)"
          cleancontaminatedbowel: "Clean-contaminated (bowel opened, little or `normal` spillage)"
          contaminated: "Contaminated (e.g. bowel opened, gross spillage)"
          infected: "Infected = Dirty (infection present in the operative field: skin; soft tissue; urinary tract, etc.)"
          nointervention: "No Intervention = No intervention took place"
      diagnosedate:
        question:
          uti: "Date when UTI was diagnosed (can be different from the Study-day)"
          ssi: "Date when SSI was diagnosed (can be different from the Study-day)"
      clinicaldiagnosis:
        quesion: "Clinical diagnosis"
        answers:
          uti:
            cystitis: "Cystitis (grade of severity:1)"
            pyelonephritis_moderate: "Pyelonephritis, moderate (grade of severity:2)"
            pyelonephritis_severe: "Pyelonephritis, severe/established (grade of severity:3)"
            urosepsissimple: "Urosepsis (simple) (grade of severity:4)"
            urosepsissevere: "Severe urosepsis (grade of severity:5)"
            urosepsisshock: "Uroseptic shock (grade of severity:6)"
            other: "Other"
          ssi:
            urosepsissimple: "Urosepsis (simple)"
            urosepsissevere: "Severe urosepsis"
            urosepsisshock: "Uroseptic shock"
            pyelonephritis_moderate: "Pyelonephritis, moderate"
            pyelonephritis_severe: "Pyelonephritis, severe/established"
            cystitis: "Cystitis"
            asymptomatic: "Asymptomatic bacteriuria"
            epididymoorchitis: "Epididymoorchitis"
            prostatitis: "Prostatitis"
            other: "Other"
      clinicaldiagnosisspecify:
        quesion: "Please specify"
        help: "English text"
      cdc:
        question:
          uti: "Which CDC criteria were used for UTI diagnosis? CDC UTI Definitions"
          ssi: "Clinical definitions of SSI according to CDC"
      symptomaticutiandbacteriuria:
        answers: "Symptomatic UTI AND bacteriuria"
      symptomaticutiandother:
        answers: "Symptomatic UTI AND other signs of infection"
      asymptomaticbactcath:
        answers: "Asymptomatic bacteriuria catheter associated"
      asymptomaticbactnocath:
        answers: "Asymptomatic bacteriuria without catheter use"
      otheruti:
        answers: "Other infections of the urinary tract"
      superficialssi:
        answers: "Superficial incisional SSI"
      deepssi:
        answers: "Deep incisional SSI"
      organssi:
        answers: "Organ/space SSI"
      provennauti:
        question:
          uti: "Is the patient considered to have a microbiologically proven UTI?"
          ssi: "Is the patient considered to have a microbiologically proven SSI?"
      culturetissue_urine:
        answers: "Urine"
      culturetissue_blood:
        answers: "Blood"
      culturetissue_fluidswab:
        answers:
          uti: "Fluid/swab from UTI"
          ssi: "Fluid/swab from SSI"
      culturetissue_other:
        answers: "Other"
      culturetissue_specify:
        answers: "Please specify"
        help: "English text"
      antibioticculture:
        question: "Was the patient receiving antibiotics when culture was taken?"
        answers:
          "yes": 'Yes'
          "no": 'No'
          unknown: Unknown
      antimicrobical_treatment:
        question: "Administration of antimicrobial treatment"
        answers:
          none: "No treatment"
          oral: "Oral"
          parenteral: "Parenteral"
          both: "Both"
      treatment_antibiotics:
        question: "The antimicrobial drugs belong to the following groups"
